Guide to the Samuel R. Delany Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- May 2017 acquisition, 200.17; (249 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Materials deposited in June 2000, circa 1998; 0.42; (1 box)
    - Manuscripts by SRD, circa 1998
      - 'Shoat Rumblin', 1998 September 1, undated (Box 79)
        Contains: 2 computerscript drafts, one with text revisions.
      - "A Commentary on Hart Crane's 'The Bridge'", undated (Box 79)
        Contains: computerscript.
  - Materials deposited in July 2000, 1983-2000; 6.92; (7 boxes)
    These materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University. Samuel R. Delany deposited them in July 2000.
    - Manuscripts, 1997-2000-06
      - By SRD, 1997-2000-06
        - 'Shoat Rumblin', 1998-05-2000-06 (Box 80)
          Contains: complete drafts; "Part I" drafts; "Part II" drafts; "Part III" drafts; assorted draft segments.
        - 'Shoat Rumblin', 1999-05-30-1999-10-30 (Box 81)
          Contains: complete drafts; "Part II" drafts; assorted draft segments (excerpt with holograph corrections to be published in 'Callaloo' magazine).
        - 'Times Square Red, Times Square Blue', 1998-10-1999-12 (Box 81)
          Contains: preface with holograph corrections (folder 1); corrections list (folder 1); list of typographical errors (folder 11).
        - 'Shorter Views', 1999 (Box 81)
          Contains: galley proofs with holograph corrections. Pages 1-223 in folder 2, pages 224-464 in folder 3.
        - 'Dhalgren', undated (Box 81)
          Contains: list of corrections. Includes: holograph notes.
        - '1984: The Collected Letters of Samuel Delany', 1999-11-05 (Box 80)
          Contains: galley proofs.
        - '1984: The Collected Letters of Samuel Delany', 1999-11-05 (Box 81)
        - Essays, 1997(?) (Box 80)
          Contains: "3,2,1, Contact: Times Square Red, 1997".
        - Essays, undated (Box 81)
          Contains: "Historifying Marginal Practices", incomplete (folder 1); "The Owls; or Death and the Labyrinth" (folder 1); New York in the Year Three Thousand" (folder 2).
        - Interviews, undated, 1999 (Box 81)
          Contains: text of "Interview with James Morrow" for 'Paradoxa' (undated); galley proofs of "Interview with James Morrow" (1999).
        - Notebooks, 1999-07-2000-05; (5 folders) (Box 81)
          Contains: red cover, including correspondence, news clippings, and professional materials (1999 September - October); dark blue cover, including professional materials (1999 August - September); bright blue cover, including personal memorabilia and correspondence (2000 April - May); bright blue cover #2, including personal memorabilia (1999 December - 2000 January); purple cover, including correspondence, news clippings, and personal memorabilia (1999 July 4 - 1999 August). All notebooks include holograph notes.
      - By others, 1999-09-30-1999-10
        - Rowell, C.: Interview with SRD, undated (Box 80)
        - Czyz, Vincent: "A Written Interview with Samuel Delany", 1999-10 (Box 81)
          Contains: 2 drafts, 3 copies.
        - Riedel, Bob: "Interview with Samuel R. Delany", 1999-10- (Box 81)
          Contains: 2 copies.
        - The St. Marks Poetry Project: "A Silent Interview with Samuel Delany", undated (Box 81)
          Contains: incomplete draft.
        - De Man, Paul: "Literary History and Literary Modernity", 1999-09-30 (Box 81)
          Contains: printout from Harvard website with holograph notes by SRD.
        - Freedman, Carl: "An Anatomy of Hope" (review of '1984: Selected Letters' by SRD), undated (Box 81)
          Contains: computerscript with holograph notes.
    - Printed material, 1997-2000
      - By SRD, 1997-2000-03
        - Magazine articles, 1997 (Box 80)
          Contains: excerpt from 'Phallos!' and synopsis of 'Phallos!', published in 'Callaloo', Vol. 20, No. 1.
        - Magazine articles, circa 1997-1999 (Box 81)
          Contains: 2 copies of excerpt from 'Phallos!' and synopsis of 'Phallos!', published in 'Callaloo', Vol. 20, No. 1 (folder 18); excerpt from 'Shoat Rumblin', published in 'Callaloo', Vol. 23, No. 1 (folder 19); introduction to "Smoke, Lilies, and Jade" by Richard Bruce Nugent, published in 'The James White Review' (folder 19); "The Reinvention of Hart Crane" including holograph notes, published in 'The Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review' (folder 19); "Interview with James Morrow", published in 'Paradoxa', Vol. 5, No. 12 (folder 21).
        - Magazine articles, 1999-12-30 (Box 82)
          Contains: "Sin City Before Sony", published in 'San Francisco Frontiers Newsmagazine'.
        - Newspaper articles, 1999-11-2000-01 (Box 82)
          Contains: laminated newspaper articles. Includes: "Samuel Delany Imagines New York City Circa 3000", published in 'Village Voice' (2000 January 4); "Antidote to Tedium", published in 'New York Press' (1999 November 10-16); letter re: circumcision, published in 'New York Press' (1999 November 24-30).
        - Newspaper articles, 1999 November - 2000 February/March (Box 81)
          Contains: "Samuel Delany Imagines New York City Circa 3000", published in 'Village Voice'; "Fiction 2000" by SRD and others, published in 'Village Voice'; "Antidote to Tedium", published in 'New York Press'
        - Books, 1999 (Box 81)
          Contains: 'They Fly at Ciron', Spanish version, paperback.
      - Re: SRD, 1998-2000
        - Reviews, 1999 December / 2000 January (Box 80)
          Contains: 'On Our Backs' review of 'Times Square Red, Times Square Blue'.
        - Reviews, circa 1999 - 2000 (Box 81)
          Contains: photocopies of approximately 15 magazine and newspaper reviews of 'Times Square Red, Times Square Blue' (folder 18); 'Rain Taxi' review of 'Bread and Wine' (folder 17); 'Publishers Weekly' review of '1984: The Collected Letters' (folder 19).
        - Reviews, 1999-10-12-1999-11-28 (Box 82)
          Contains: 'New York Times Book Review' review of 'Times Square Red, Times Square Blue', laminated article (1999 November 28); 'Village Voice Literary Supplement' with SRD at #10 on bestselers list (1999 October 12).
        - Interviews with SRD, 2000-08 (Box 80)
          Contains: 'Vibe' interview with SRD.
        - Interviews with SRD, 1998 - 2000 summer (Box 81)
          Contains: 'New Millenium Writings' profile by Vincent Czyz (2000 summer) (folder 22); interview in 'Paradoxa', Vol. 4, No. 11 (1998) (folder 21).
        - Other about SRD, 1998 (Box 80)
          Contains: flier for "February at The Poetry Project", SRD speaking with Will Alexander.
        - Other about SRD, 1998-1999 (Box 81)
          Contains: "Sci-Fi Finds a Home at UB", published in 'Generation' (1999 October 26); program from "Voyages: The 25th World Fantasy Convention" with SRD listed as "Special Guest", including article and bibliography (1999 November 4 - November 7); photocopies of magazine and news articles on Delany and his words (1998 May - 1999 August); "Strangers in Stranger Lands", published in 'THe Writer's Chronicle" (1999 December); University at Buffalo Department of English newsletter, mentioning 'The Motion of Light in Water' (1999 October); bulletin for The English Institute's 58th session at Harvard University, "Tense/Times: Literature, Anxiety, Temporality", listing SRD as speaker for 1999 October 3; printed cards for 'Bread and Wine' publication party, 2 copies.
        - Other about SRD, 1999-04-29-2000-02-28 (Box 85)
          Contains: black and white poster for lecture at State University of New York at Fredonia (2000 February 28); poster for lecture at Rensselaer Polytechnic, 2 plain copies, 8 copies signed by SRD (1999 April 29).
      - Other, 1999-10-04
        - Two articles by others, 1999-10-04 (Box 81)
          Contains: fax copies of 2 articles by others published in 'Paradoxa', Vol. 5, No. 12. Includes: "A Vulnerable Atheist" by James Morrow; "Lord, What Fools These Mortals Be!" by Brian Stableford.
    - Professional material, 1999-2000
      - SRD teaching materials, 1999
        - Class list for "Art and Revolution", 1999 fall (Box 83)
        - Synopses for courses "Long Dark Poems" and "Creative Writing", undated (Box 83)
        - Course book for "Introduction to Literary Theory", undated (Box 83)
          Contains: copy with holograph notes.
      - Other, 1999-2000
        - Copy of airline itinerary for trip to Buffalo, New York, 1999-09-1999-10 (Box 83)
        - Name tag from 30th Annual Comic-Con International, 1999 (Box 83)
        - Name tag from 25th World Fantasy Convention, 1999 (Box 83)
        - Pages from SRD's 1999 planner book (Box 83)
          Contains: pages with holograph notes.
        - Program from 25th World Fantasy Convention with SRD listed as "Special Guest", 1999 (Box 83)
        - Flier advertising publishing party for '1984: Selected Letters', circa 2000 (Box 83)
          Contains: 2 copies of flier.
        - Fliers and map from 26th New Year's Marathon Reading, 1999-12-30-2000-01-01 (Box 83)
          Contains: 2 copies of fliers and map; schedule card.
    - Personal memorabilia, 1983-1999
      - Plaque from Forbidden Planet Scifi and Comic Art Convention, with SRD as 1983 Guest of Honor (Box 84)
      - Program book from "Heaven" art exhibit at Tate Gallery, 1999 (Box 83)
    - Audiovisual material, circa 1999
      - Audio material, circa 1999
        - Cassette set from OutWrite 1999 conference, with SRD on "Science Fiction Workshop" tape, circa 1999; 6 (Box 244)
      - Video material, 1999-12-11
        - SRD, "The What Whitman of Times Square" at Judson Memorial Church, 1999-12-11; 1 (Box 244)
    - Correspondence, 1999-09-2000-06
      - Letters, emails, and faxes to and from SRD, 1999-09-2000-06; (3 folders) (Box 83)
        Contains: assorted computerscript and holograph letters, emails, and faxes to and from SRD.
    - Financial/legal material, 2000-03-03
      - Invoice to SRD from Steven B. Tamarin, M.D., 2000-03-03 (Box 80)
  - Materials deposited in December 2000, 1.08; (1 box)
    These materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University. Samuel R. Delany deposited them in December 2000.
    - Correspondence, 2000
      - Professional and personal correspondence, 2000 (Box 86)
        Contains: professional and personal correspondence, mostly e-mail. Approximately 1500 pages total.
    - Printed material, undated
      - Web printouts, programs, reviews, blurbs, undated (Box 86)
    - Professional material, undated
      - Professional material, including information re: royalties, undated (Box 86)
  - Materials deposited prior to 2002, 1973-02-03-1998; 3.08; (4 boxes)
    These materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University. Samuel R. Delany deposited them prior to 2002.
    - Student and faculty evaluations, circa 1989 - 1998 (Box 247)
      Restricted until 2073. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
    - Report of psychological study of Iva Hacker-Delany, 1985-01-25 (Box 248)
      Contains: typescript report in the form of a letter.
      Restricted until 2060. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
    - Correspondence: Joe and Pat Muir to SRD, 1973-02-03 (Box 87)
      - Correspondence: note and drawing from Pat Muir to SRD (hand with LSD tab), 1973-02-03 (Box 249 (Oversize))
    - Draft of SRD to Robert S. Bravard, circa 1987 (Box 87)
  - Materials deposited in 2002, 1968-08-2002; 7.0; (7 boxes)
    These materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University. Samuel R. Delany deposited them in 2002.
    - Manuscripts, 2001-06-2001-08
      - By SRD, undated
        - 'Shoat Rumblin', parts 1-3, undated; (3 folders) (Box 91)
        - "The Owls", undated; (2 folders) (Box 91)
          Contains: various excerpts with holograph corrections.
        - Various short stories and essays, undated (Box 91)
      - "Letters from Amherst", undated (Box 91)
        Contains: a collection of 5 narrative letters from SRD presented as a manuscript.
      - Short stories and essays by various authors including Carl Freedman, Rick Polney, and others, undated (Box 91)
      - Excerpt from "Phallos"; prelude to 'Shoat Rumblin'; "Images of City and Psyche in the Life of a Gay Poet", undated (Box 91)
      - 'Dhalgren' screenplays, undated; 2001
        - 'Dhalgren' screenplay by Reith-Lex, undated (Box 91)
        - 'Dhalgren' screenplay by John P. Flynn, undated (Box 91)
        - Photocopied pages with holograph corrections, undated (Box 88)
        - Revisions, 2001-06-2001-08 (Box 88)
      - Draft segments of 'The Mad Man', undated (Box 88)
        Contains: several draft segments of 'The Mad Man'.
      - Corrections for various short works, undated (Box 88)
    - Printed material, 1968-08-2002
      - Biographical materials re: SRD and reading Delany, undated (Box 88)
      - Various interviews with SRD, undated (Box 88)
      - Reviews of works by SRD, undated (Box 88)
      - Bound essays re: 'The Motion of Light in Water', undated (Box 88)
      - Bound photocopied excerpts from works by SRD, undated (Box 88)
      - "Nova" (by SRD), undated; (2 folders) (Box 88)
      - "Kaczynski - a meditation" by Gerald Burns, undated (Box 88)
        Contains: "Kaczynski - a meditation" and other essays.
      - Magazines and journals, 1968-08-2002
        - 'Vibe', 2000-08-2001-06 (Box 88)
          Contains: 3 issues of 'Vibe' (2000 August, 2001 March, 2001 June).
        - 'Rain Taxi', 2000/2001 winter (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'Rain Taxi'.
        - 'Poets and Writers', 2002-01-2002-02 (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'Poets and Writers'.
        - 'Gay and Lesbian Review Worldwide', 2001-01-2001-02 (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'Gay and Lesbian Review Worldwide'.
        - 'Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review', 1999 fall (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review'.
        - 'Genre', 2001-08 (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'Genre'.
        - 'Inches', 2001-11 (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'Inches'.
        - 'The Advocate', 2002-01-22 (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'The Advocate'.
        - 'New York', 2001-06-04 (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'New York'.
        - 'Entertainment', 2001-06-08 (Box 88)
          Contais: 1 issue of 'Entertainment'.
        - 'Matrix', undated (Box 88)
          Contains: (at least) 1 issue of 'Matrix'.
        - 'Multitudes', 2002 spring (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'Multitudes'.
        - 'Vintage', 2001 summer (Box 88)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'Vintage'.
        - "Yaddo Annual Report", 2000 (Box 88)
        - 'New Millennium Writings', 2000 summer (Box 93)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'New Millennium Writings'.
        - 'The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction', 1968-08-2002-02 (Box 93)
          Contains: 3 issues of 'The Magazine of Fantasy and Science Fiction' (1968 August, 1977 October, 2002 February).
        - Setter's proof of 'Longer Views', undated (Box 93)
          Contains: setter's proof of 'Longer Views' by SRD. Includes: "Wagner/Artaud" (?).
        - 'Nightlines Weekly', 2001-05-16 (Box 93)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'Nightlines Weekly'.
        - 'Help Yourself', "The Unbearables", undated (Box 93)
        - 'Differences', Journal of Feminist Cultural Studies, undated (Box 93)
        - 'Transition - An International Review', "Knowledge and Tradition", undated (Box 93)
        - 'MR', #47/48, undated (Box 93)
        - 'TriQuarterly 49 Science Fiction', undated (Box 93)
        - 'The Yale Journal of Criticism', 1994 spring (Box 93)
          Contains: 1 issue of 'The Yale Journal of Criticism'.
        - 'Flame Wars' by Mark Dery, 1993 fall (Box 93)
      - Excerpt from 'Phallos', undated; (2 folders) (Box 88)
        Contains: 30 copies of excerpt from 'Phallos'.
      - Printed material re: teaching English courses, SFRA Cleveland 2000; miscellaneous pamphlets, circa 2000, undated (Box 88)
      - Page proofs by SRD, undated
        - 'The Mad Man', undated (Box 92)
          Contains: discarded version (folder 24); bound draft (folder 26).
        - 'Empire Star', undated (Box 92)
          Contains: pages 1-90 with cover letter (folder 25); bound draft (folder 27).
        - 'Dhalgren', undated (Box 92)
          Contains: plastic-bound draft/proof, 2 copies (folders 28-29); advanced reader's proof, 2 copies (folder 30).
      - "On Dhalgren", undated (Box 92)
        Contains: "On Dhalgren", plastic bound. Inludes: reviews, reactions, corrections.
      - Newspaper and laminated clippings re: SRD, undated (Box 94 (Oversize))
      - Announcements and posters for lectures by SRD, undated (Box 94 (Oversize))
      - "Historical Perspectives on Depression" by Paul Roazen, 1980 (Box 94 (Oversize))
        Contains: "Historical Perspectives on Depression", printed booklet.
      - Event posters, 2000-10-2000-11 (Box 94 (Oversize))
        Contains: "Global Humanities 2000 Symposium" poster, autographed by J.M Coetzee (2000 October); Laurie Toby Edison art exhibition poster (2000 November).
    - Correspondence, 1997-2002
      - General, 1997-2002; (6 folders) (Box 90)
        Contains: emails and signed computerscript letters.
      - From David Hyde, 2001 (Box 90)
        Includes: interview.
      - From Iva Hacker-Delany, 2001 (Box 90)
      - From Vince Czyz, 2001 (Box 90)
        Contains: emails.
      - From Jeffrey Tucker, 2001-2002 (Box 90)
      - From Gil Roth, 2001-2002 (Box 90)
      - From Kelly Salmon, 1999-2002 (Box 90)
      - From Carl Freedman, 2001-2002; (2 folders) (Box 90)
      - From Marilyn Hacker, 2001 (Box 90)
      - From Israel Shaw, Elayne Tobin, Randy Byers, Dorothea Lobermann, Peggy Delany, Rick Polney, 2001-2002 (Box 90)
      - From Edward Kastenmeier, R. L. Caserio, Justine Larbalestier, undated (Box 90)
      - Joshua B. Lukin, Sharon Marcus, undated (Box 90)
        Contains: emails and computerscript letters.
      - Ron Drummond, 2001 (Box 90)
      - Mailing list for discussion of works by SRD, 2001-2002; (4 folders) (Box 92)
    - Financial material, 2001
      - Bank receipts, 2001 (Box 93)
    - Photographs and artwork, 2000-2001
      - Photoprints and drawing of SRD, circa 2000 - 2001 (Box 89)
        Contains: photoprints of SRD with accompanying letter; drawing of SRD.
    - Personal memorabilia, 1999-2001
      - Badges, circa 1999 (Box 93)
        Contains: badges for SRD from 'Readercon' 11-13; badge worn at presentation of Hart Crane biography.
      - 2001 sunglasses (Box 93)
        Contains: 1 broken pair of 2001 New Year celebratory sunglasses.
      - Handwritten card with picture of baby inside, 2001-04-01 (Box 93)
    - Notebooks, undated
      - Various notebooks, undated; (5 folders) (Box 91)
        Contains: various notebooks. Includes: financial documents.
  - Materials deposited in 2003, 1969-2003; 7.42; (7 boxes)
    These materials were previously held on deposit at the Howard Gotlieb Archival Research Center, Boston University. Samuel R. Delany deposited them in 2003.
    - Manuscripts, 1969-2003
      - By SRD, 1969-2003
        - 'Phallos', circa 2003; (5 folders) (Box 95)
          Contains: typescript draft, including appendix; bound excerpt, 5 copies, including "Working Version", "Revision May 2003", and "Final Version".
        - 'Hogg', 1969; (4 folders) (Box 95)
          Contains: uncorrected copy, typescript; photocopy of typescript.
        - 'The Brief Day of Sun and Frost' a.k.a. 'This Short Day of Sun and Frost', 2002-08-2003-04; (4 folders) (Box 95)
          Contains: 2 drafts, typescript; 3 bound drafts, typescript.
        - 'Four', 1992-05 (Box 95)
          Contains: bound typescript.
        - 'Shoat Rumblin', "His Sensations and Ideas Part I", 2001-01 (Box 95)
        - "Some Queer Notions About Race", 1998-10 (Box 95)
        - "Beatitudes", 1997-06 (Box 95)
        - "The Prize", 2002-12-08 (Box 95)
          Contains: 2 typescript drafts.
        - "A Centennial Life from the Roaring Twenties", review of "The Broken Tower: The Life of Hart Crane" by Paul Mariani, 1999-05 (Box 95)
        - "Adam Roberts Interviews Samuel R. Delany", 2003-07 (Box 95)
          Contains: typescript (?). Also includes: correspondence (2003 July); holograaph notes; preface by SRD.
        - "A Delany Miscellany: Amherst Stuff", undated; (2 folders) (Box 95)
          Contains: typescript. Includes: printed material; essay; excerpts by SRD.
        - "Fiction, Poetry, and Sex in Joanna Russ's 'Souls'", undated (Box 95)
      - By various authors, 1997-06-2000-12-12
        - Bast, Andrew: 'Synopsis of Laugh Decadence' (novel), undated (Box 95)
        - Steiner, Leslie K.: "Anatomy of a Nova", 1997-06 (Box 95)
        - Steiner, Leslie K.: "Samuel R. Delany", undated (Box 95)
        - Vitrano, Michael: "Take Home Exam", response questions, 2000-12-12 (Box 95)
        - Vitrano, Michael: "Heart of Darkness" paper re-write, undated (Box 95)
        - Miscellaneous typescript(s) re: various manuscripts, undated (Box 95)
        - Unknown author: fragments, undated (Box 95)
        - Unknown author: "III Marx/Nietzsche/Freud/Nixon", undated (Box 95)
    - Notebooks, 1997-2002-08
      - Notebook, 2002-08 (Box 96)
      - Phone message book, 1997 (Box 96)
      - Notebook, 2002-06 (Box 96)
      - Notebook, undated (Box 96)
      - Notebook, undated (Box 96)
    - Subject files, 2001-2002
      - Untitled file, 2001-2002
        - Manuscript material for 'The Brief Day of Sun and Frost', undated (Box 96)
        - Correspondence, undated (Box 96)
        - Printed poster for a World Trade Center Memorial, circa 2001 - 2002 (Box 96)
      - "Fire and Ink: A Writer's Festival for LGBT People of African Descent", undated (Box 96)
        Includes: pass.
    - Correspondence, 1984-2003
      - Files, 1984-2003-01-17
        - "Letters, 7/7/9-4/5/91", 1990-07-07-1991-04-05; (3 folders) (Box 96)
          Contains: typed letters from SRD.
        - "1984 -- Volume III", (2 folders) (Box 96)
          Contains: typed letters from SRD. Includes: cover page.
        - "Letters -- Philmos etc.", undated; (3 folders) (Box 96)
          Contains: typed letters from SRD. Includes: manuscript material.
        - Untitled, undated (Box 96)
          Contains: typed letters from SRD. Includes: "Beatitudes" manuscript.
        - Bound collections of emails re: "Mailing List for the Discussion of the Works of Samuel R. Delany", 2002-05-31-2003-01-17; (7 folders) (Box 96)
          Contains: 7 bound email collections.
      - Emails, mostly professional, to and from SRD, 2001-2003; (9 folders) (Box 97)
        Contains: approximately 900 emails. Includes: emails to and from students at Temple University.
      - Typed letters, mostly professional or student-related, from SRD, 2002-2003; (3 folders) (Box 97)
        Contains: 59 typed letters. Includes: 10 letters on Temple University letterhead re: recommendations for tenure.
      - Contract for poetry reading, undated (Box 97)
        Contains: fax of contract for poetry reading.
      - Typed letters from SRD re: payment for his apartment and to the IRS, 2002-08-2003-06 (Box 97)
        Contains: 23 typed letters from SRD.
      - Typed letter from NYU Press announcing book publication, undated (Box 97)
        Contains: signed typed letter.
    - Printed material, 1999-2003-05
      - Proofs, undated
        - "Aye and Gomorrah", undated; (3 folders) (Box 97)
          Contains: 2 sets of proofs.
        - "Time Considered as a Helix of Semi-Precious Stones", undated; (2 folders) (Box 97)
        - "Driftglass/Starshards", undated; (3 folders) (Box 98)
      - Bound proofs, undated
        - 'Times Square Red, Times Square Blue', undated (Box 98)